A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1 FA772
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Events, 1
  - Kenneth Lieberthal Briefing and Dinner, 2000 May 2 (Box 19, Folder 363)
  - Internet Panel Program, 2000 May 17 (Box 19, Folder 364)
    Capitol Hill Program on the Information Revolution in China. Hart Senate Office Building. Cosponsored with the Asia Society.
  - James Soong Luncheon Meeting, 2000 May 22 (Box 19, Folder 365)
    NCUSCR Office. Soong was the former provincial governor of Taiwan.
  - Zhao Qizheng Roundtable Discussion, 2000 June 21 (Box 19, Folder 366)
  - John Kamm Briefing, 2000 July 18 (Box 19, Folder 367)
  - Ambassador Mei Zhaorong Meeting, 2000 August 8 (Box 19, Folder 368)
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon - General, 2000 September 8 (Box 19, Folder 369)
    Waldorf-Astoria. Cosponsored with the U.S. - China Business Council. Planning and Correspondence with Cosponsors.
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon - Chinese Embassy / Mission, 2000 September 8 (Box 19, Folder 370)
    File includes translation of Jiang's speech and list of Chinese guests.
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon - Hotel Issues, 2000 September 8 (Box 20, Folder 371)
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon - Media File, 2000 September 8 (Box 20, Folder 372)
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon - Press Clippings, 2000 September 8 (Box 20, Folder 373)
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon - Registrants, 2000 September 8 (Box 20, Folder 374)
  - Jiang Zemin Luncheon - Security, 2000 September 8 (Box 20, Folder 375)
  - Heilongjiang Province Delegation, 2000 September (Box 20, Folder 376)
  - Peter Woo, Hong Kong Trade Development (HKTDC), Meeting, 2000 October 25 (Box 20, Folder 377)
  - Nicholas D. Kristof and Sheryl WuDunn Program, 2000 November 9 (Box 20, Folder 378)
  - Minister of Education Chen Zhili Visit (Cancelled), 2000 November 18 (Box 20, Folder 379)
  - Annual Members' Address and Reception, 2000 November 30 (Box 20, Folder 380)
  - Board of Directors' Dinner, 2000 November 30 (Box 20, Folder 381)
  - Board of Directors' Meeting, 2000 December 1 (Box 20, Folder 382)
  - Youthful Voices Discussion (Time Warner Interns), 2000 December 6 (Box 20, Folder 383)
    China Institute
  - Youthful Voices Discussion (Time Warner Interns), 2000 December 6; FA772:019; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 383)
    2 snapshots of participants
  - Taiwan's Political Turmoil Panel, 2001 January 9 (Box 20, Folder 384)
    Heritage Foundation, Washington, DC
  - Same Bed, Different Dreams, David M. Lampton Book Discussion, 2001 January 9 and 29 (Box 20, Folder 385)
    Nixon Center, Washington, DC (January 9); Council on Foreign Relations (January 29).
  - Justin Yifu Lin Corporate Briefing, 2001 January 10 (Box 20, Folder 386)
    Metropolitan Life International
  - Judicial Reform Roundtable (Zou Bihua), 2001 January 31 (Box 20, Folder 387)
  - Joseph W. Prueher Corporate Briefing, 2001 February 14 (Box 20, Folder 388)
  - Zhou Mingwei Events, 2001 February 20 (Box 20, Folder 389)
    Masonic Hall. Roundtable discussion on Cross-Strait Relations, and Luncheon address.
  - The Tiananmen Papers Examined Panel Discussion, 2001 February 23, April 26, May 29 (Box 20, Folder 390)
    Harvard University. See also New York panel on April 26, and San Diego panel on May 29.
  - The Tiananmen Papers Examined Panel Discussion, 2001 February 23; FA772:020; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 390)
    2 snapshots of panel.
  - China Confidential, Nancy Bernkopf Tucker Program, 2001 March 12 (Box 20, Folder 391)
  - Qian Qichen Luncheon, 2001 March 23 (Box 21, Folder 392)
  - Qian Qichen Luncheon, 2001 March 23; FA772:021; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 392)
    6 snapshots of Qian and others.
  - Ambassador Yang Jiechi Luncheon, 2001 March 29 (Box 21, Folder 393)
    Ritz Carlton, Washington, DC
  - Ambassador Yang Jiechi Luncheon, 2001 March 29; FA772:022; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 393)
    1 black and white professional photo of Yang Jiechi speaking to unidentified woman.
  - Ambassador Yang Jiechi Luncheon (Hotel Arrangements), 2001 March 29 (Box 21, Folder 394)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations Lecture Series, 2001 April 11, May 8, June 5 (Box 21, Folder 395)
    Lectures by James R Sasser, Kenneth Lieberthal, and Yang Jiechi, on Redefining the U.S.-China Relationship. Cosponsored with the Chicago Council.
  - The Tiananmen Papers Examined Panel Discussion, 2001 April 26 (Box 21, Folder 396)
    Union Club, New York
  - Corporate Member Conference Call, 2001 May 14 (Box 21, Folder 397)
    On Recent Developments in U.S.-China Relations: Implications for American Business.
  - The Tiananmen Papers Panel, 2001 May 29 (Box 21, Folder 398)
    University of California, San Diego
  - Lori Esposito Murray Meetings, 2001 August 28 (Box 21, Folder 399)
    New York. Murray was director of the U.S.-China Security Review Commission.
  - Donald Tsang Breakfast Briefing and Luncheon, 2001 September 10 (Box 21, Folder 400)
    Harvard Club and Waldorf-Astoria
  - Tang Jiaxuan Dinner, 2001 September 20 (Box 21, Folder 401)
    Willard Inter-Continental Hotel, Washington, DC. Dinner for the Minister of Foreign Affairs, cosponsored by the United States - China Business Council.
  - Tang Jiaxuan Dinner, 2001 September 20 (Box 21, Folder 402)
  - Counter-Terrorism Meeting, 2001 October 5 (Box 21, Folder 403)
    Cosponsored with the Brookings Institution, Washington, DC.
  - Asian-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) Summit Fax Broadcast, 2001 October 20-21 (Box 21, Folder 404)
    NCUSCR circulated commentary on the APEC summit's economic and political outcomes and effect on U.S. - China relations.
  - Zi Zhongyun Program, 2001 October 27 (Box 22, Folder 405)
  - Corporate Member Conference Call, 2001 November 8 (Box 22, Folder 406)
    On Recent Legal Developments and Trends in China: Meeting the Challenge of WTO Accession; with Jamie Horsley and Stanley Lubman.
  - Taiwan's Legislative Yuan Elections E-mail Broadcast, 2001 December 3 (Box 22, Folder 407)
  - Annual Members' Meeting and Reception, 2001 December 6 (Box 22, Folder 408)
    Citigroup. Address by Richard C. Holbrooke, U.S. - China Relations in the Post-9/11 World.
  - Board Dinner and Meeting, 2001 December 6-7 (Box 22, Folder 409)
    Citigroup and Harvard Club
  - Hu Angang Corporate Program, 2001 December 11 (Box 22, Folder 410)
    Harvard Club. Briefing on Corruption in China.
  - Zhou Mingwei Discussion on Cross-Strait Relations, 2002 January 14 (Box 22, Folder 411)
    AOL Time Warner.
  - President Bush's Visit to Northeast Asia E-mail Broadcast, 2002 February 15 (Box 22, Folder 412)
  - Press Corps Reunion, Thirtieth Anniversary of Nixon's Trip to China, 2002 March 5 (Box 22, Folder 413)
    National Press Club, Washington, DC
  - Press Corps Reunion, Thirtieth Anniversary of Nixon's Trip to China, 2002 March 5 (Box 22, Folder 414)
    File contains compilation of press coverage, "February, 1972 Redux."
  - Press Corps Reunion, Thirtieth Anniversary of Nixon's Trip to China (Henry Kissinger Speech), 2002 March 5 (Box 22, Folder 415)
    Kissinger speech at the National Press Club and roundtable discussion on U.S.- China Relations.
  - Nicholas Lardy Book Program, 2002 March 6 (Box 22, Folder 416)
    Cosponsored with the Asia Society, for Lardy's Integrating China into the Global Economy.
  - "China and the 'stans" Panel, 2002 March 25 (Box 22, Folder 417)
    Cosponsored with the China Institute.
  - Email Broadcast on Hu Jintao, 2002 April 23 (Box 22, Folder 418)
    By Ezra Vogel.
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - General, 2002 May 1 (Box 22, Folder 419)
    Dinner at the Capital Hilton, Washington, DC, in honor of Vice President Hu. File includes program and speech.
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Budget and Invoices, 2002 May 1 (Box 22, Folder 420)
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Cosponsors, 2002 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 421)
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Embassy, 2002 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 422)
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Hotel, 2002 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 423)
    Capital Hilton, Washington, DC
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Interpreting and Audio/Video, 2002 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 424)
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Press, 2002 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 425)
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Registration, 2002 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 426)
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Registration (Individual), 2002 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 427)
    List of registrants by table.
  - Hu Jintao Dinner - Security, 2002 May 1 (Box 23, Folder 428)
  - Investing in China's Capital Markets Conference, 2002 May 9 (Box 23, Folder 429)
    One-day conference in collaboration with the Asia Society.
  - Antony Leung Breakfast Briefing, 2002 June 4 (Box 23, Folder 430)
    Asia Society
  - Ambassador Clark T. Randt Jr. Corporate Luncheon, 2002 June 12 (Box 23, Folder 431)
    Yale Club
  - Capitol Hill Programs, 2002 September 25 and October 9 (Box 23, Folder 432)
    Dirksen Senate Office Building. Programs on China in Transition and on Taiwan and U. S. Policy.
  - Three Parties, Three Views - Cross-Strait Policy in Taiwan Panel, 2002 October 8 (Box 23, Folder 433)
    Masonic Hall, New York
  - Sino-American Cooperation in World War II Symposium, 2002 October 18 (Box 23, Folder 434)
    Woodrow Wilson Center, Washington, DC
  - Jiang Visits Crawford E-mail Broadcast, 2002 October 28 (Box 23, Folder 435)
    By John Holden
  - David Zweig Brown Bag Lunch Discussion, 2002 November 11 (Box 23, Folder 436)
    NCUSCR Office. Zweig was professor at the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology.
  - Annual Members' Meeting, 2002 December 5 (Box 24, Folder 437)
    Warwick Hotel. Luncheon Address by Richard N. Haass on "China and the Future o U. S. - China Relations."
  - Board Meeting, 2002 December 6 (Box 24, Folder 438)
  - Hsiao Hsin-Huang Roundtable Discussion, 2003 January 21 (Box 24, Folder 439)
    New York. On topic of Taiwan's Social Transformation.
  - William J. Perry, North Korea Programs, 2003 January 23-24 (Box 24, Folder 440)
    Japan Society, New York; Brookings Institution, Washington, DC
  - Michael Jemal (Haier America) Corporate Luncheon, 2003 February 4 (Box 24, Folder 441)
  - China in the Red Film Screening and Discussion, 2003 February 10 (Box 24, Folder 442)
    Cosponsored with the Asia Society.
  - Christian Murck Program, 2003 March 18 (Box 24, Folder 443)
    Masonic Hall, New York. On topic of China's Investment Climate.
  - Justin Yifu Lin Corporate Breakfast Briefing, 2003 April 7 (Box 24, Folder 444)
    JPMorgan Chase offices. On Economic Policies and Changes under China's New Leadership
  - David Shambaugh Book Program, 2003 April 7 (Box 24, Folder 445)
    Asia Society. For Modernizing China's Military.
  - China's Financial Markets Corporate Briefing with Laura Cha (Postponed), 2003 April 28 (Box 24, Folder 446)
    Cha postponed her trip because of the SARS outbreak.
  - SARS Conference, 2003 June 18 (Box 24, Folder 447)
    New York Life Insurance Company. On the impact of the SARS virus outbreak on China.
  - Managing Public Health Emergencies Videoconferences, 2003 July 16/17 and November 18/19 (Box 24, Folder 448)
    New York /Beijing, and New York/Shanghai
  - Managing Public Health Emergencies Videoconferences (Background Readings), 2003 July 16/17 and November 18/19 (Box 24, Folder 449)
  - Ambassador Clark T. Randt Jr. Corporate Briefing, 2003 September 10 (Box 24, Folder 450)
  - China's Financial Markets Program, 2003 September 22 (Box 24, Folder 451)
    Asia Society program. With Laura Cha.
  - Carl E. Walter Luncheon, 2003 September 23 (Box 24, Folder 452)
  - Dai Xianglong Reception, 2003 September 24 (Box 24, Folder 453)
    Ritz-Carlton, New York. Cosponsored with the U.S. - China Business Council and the Asian American Business Development Center. Dai was mayor of Tianjin.
  - National People's Congress (NPC) Delegation Luncheon, 2003 October 3 (Box 24, Folder 454)
  - Annual Members' Meeting, 2003 November 12 (Box 24, Folder 455)
    Union Club
  - Board Meeting, 2003 November 13 (Box 24, Folder 456)
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - General, 2003 December 9 (Box 24, Folder 457)
    Ritz-Carlton, Washington, DC. File includes program, speech, and budget information.
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - General, 2003 December 9; FA772:023; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 457)
    5 images of Wen and other speakers.
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - Arrangements and Planning, 2003 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 458)
    File maintained by Jan Berris.
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - Cosponsors, 2003 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 459)
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - Embassy, 2003 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 460)
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - Hotel and Interpreting Equipment, 2003 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 461)
    Ritz-Carlton, Washington, DC.
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - Press, 2003 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 462)
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - Registration, 2003 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 463)
  - Wen Jiabao Dinner - VIP Invitations, 2003 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 464)
  - Chinese Views on a Changing World Program, 2004 January 13 (Box 25, Folder 465)
    New School University. Cosponsored with the World Policy Institute.
  - Justin Yifu Lin Dinner Program, 2004 January 29 (Box 25, Folder 466)
    Harvard Club. Lin also spoke at the Asia Society on January 30.
  - "China in the WTO - A View from Geneva" Corporate Briefing, 2004 February 5 (Box 25, Folder 467)
    American International Group Offices. Briefing with Huang Rengang.
  - Ambassador Ma Zhengang Luncheon, 2004 February 18 (Box 25, Folder 468)
    Rockefeller Brothers Fund Offices. Discussion on China's Foreign Policy.
  - Dispute Resolution in China Program, 2004 February 18 (Box 25, Folder 469)
    Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison offices.
  - Taiwan's Election Results Conference Call Discussion, 2004 March 22 (Box 25, Folder 470)
  - Ian Johnson, Wild Grass, Book Program, 2004 March 29 (Box 25, Folder 471)
  - Christine Loh Discussion, 2004 March 30 (Box 25, Folder 472)
  - Worker Displacement in China Symposium, 2004 April 8 (Box 25, Folder 473)
    Washington, DC
  - Wu Yi Dinner - General, 2004 April 22 (Box 25, Folder 474)
    Fairmont Hotel, Washington, DC. File includes program, schedule, and speeches.
  - Wu Yi Dinner - Hotel, 2004 April 22 (Box 25, Folder 475)
    Fairmont Hotel, Washington, DC
  - Wu Yi Dinner - Interpreting Equipment, 2004 April 22 (Box 25, Folder 476)
  - Wu Yi Dinner - Press, 2004 April 22 (Box 25, Folder 477)
  - Wu Yi Dinner - Registration, 2004 April 22 (Box 25, Folder 478)
  - Wang Qishan Luncheon, 2004 May 12 (Box 25, Folder 479)
    Asia Society. Wang was mayor of Beijing.
  - Ambassador James Lilley, China Hands, Book Program, 2004 June 1 (Box 25, Folder 480)
  - Sustaining Momentum in China's HIV-AIDS Response Program, 2004 June 30 (Box 26, Folder 481)
    New York Life Insurance Company
  - Joseph Wu and Lin Fangmei Roundtable Discussion, 2004 July 13 (Box 26, Folder 482)
    Wu was chair of the Mainland Affairs Council
  - Hu Angang Corporate Members' Breakfast, 2004 September 23 (Box 26, Folder 483)
  - Ambassador Clark T. Randt Jr. Corporate Members' Luncheon, 2004 October 5 (Box 26, Folder 484)
  - China's Financial Markets III, 2004 October 7 (Box 26, Folder 485)
  - Dialogue on U.S. - China Economic Relations, 2004 October 26-27 (Box 26, Folder 486)
    Bell Harbor International Conference Center, Seattle
  - Annual Members' Program, 2004 November 10 (Box 26, Folder 487)
    399 Park Avenue, New York. Address by Robert Zoellick.
  - Shanghai WTO Affairs Consultation Center Delegation Luncheon, 2004 November 15 (Box 26, Folder 488)
  - Dai Bingguo Luncheon, 2004 November 29 (Box 26, Folder 489)
  - Better Hong Kong Foundation Discussion, 2005 February 14 (Box 26, Folder 490)
  - Ambassador Yang Jiechi Farewell Reception, 2005 February 28 (Box 26, Folder 491)
    Citigroup Conference Center
  - Barnett-Oksenberg Lecture on Sino-American Relations, 2005 February 28; 2013 (Box 26, Folder 492)
    Shanghai. Lecture by J. Stapleton Roy. Planning memo for 2013 lecture added to file.
  - Brookings Institution Center for Northeast Asian Policy Studies (CNAPS) Visiting Fellows Discussion, 2005 April 4 (Box 26, Folder 493)
    NCUSCR Offices
  - Wu Jianmin Breakfast Program, 2005 April 5 (Box 26, Folder 494)
    Discussion with China National Association for International Studies delegation.
  - Anti-Secession E-mail Broadcast, 2005 April 18 (Box 26, Folder 495)
    House testimony of Thomas J. Christensen, 2005 April 6. Folder dated April 18.
  - Fan Gang Program, 2005 April 21 (Box 26, Folder 496)
    Jones Day offices.
  - John Holden Farewell Reception, 2005 April (Box 26, Folder 497)
    New York. Original folder gave date as April 29.
  - Rockefeller Foundation China Project Briefing, 2005 April 22 (Box 26, Folder 498)
    The NCUSCR organized a briefing for senior leaders of the Rockefeller Foundation on the Implications of China's Rise for the Rockefeller Foundation's Strategic Directions.
  - Rockefeller Foundation China Project Briefing, 2005 April 22-2007 (Box 26, Folder 499)
  - Rockefeller Foundation China Project Briefing (Background Book), 2005 April 22 (Box 27, Folder 500)
  - Rockefeller Foundation China Project Briefing (Meeting Report), 2005 April 22 (Box 27, Folder 501)
  - Intellectual Property Rights E-mail Broadcast, 2005 April-May (Box 27, Folder 502)
  - Stephen A. Orlins Welcome Reception, 2005 May 25 (Box 27, Folder 503)
    Metropolitan Club, Washington, DC. Orlins was the new president of the NCUSCR.
  - Xu Kuangdi Dinner, 2005 June 2 (Box 27, Folder 504)
    Metropolitan Club, New York
  - Ambassador Zhou Wenzhong Reception, 2005 June 28 (Box 27, Folder 505)
    Time Warner Center
  - Revaluing China's Currency Conference Call Discussion, 2005 June 29 (Box 27, Folder 506)
  - China Institute of Contemporary International Relations (CICIR) Breakfast Discussion, 2005 July 18 (Box 27, Folder 507)
    NCUSCR office
  - Tang Jiaxuan Luncheon, 2005 July 27 (Box 27, Folder 508)
    Ritz Carlton, Washington, DC. Cosponsored by the US-China Business Council.
  - Tang Jiaxuan Luncheon, 2005 July 27 (Box 27, Folder 509)
  - China's Military Power Conference Call Discussion, 2005 August 4 (Box 27, Folder 510)
  - Hu Jintao Dinner (Cancelled), 2005 September 7 (Box 27, Folder 511)
    Mandarin Oriental Hotel, Washington, DC
  - Donald Tsang Luncheon, 2005 October 25 (Box 27, Folder 512)
  - Annual Members' Meeting, 2005 November 9 (Box 27, Folder 513)
  - Bush's Trip to China E-mail Broadcast, 2005 December 1 (Box 27, Folder 514)
  - Mark Kirk Breakfast Discussion, 2005 December 9 (Box 27, Folder 515)
  - James McGregor, One Billion Chinese, Book Discussion, 2006 January 12 (Box 27, Folder 516)
  - Li Xiguang Roundtable Discussion, 2006 February 27 (Box 27, Folder 517)
  - New Tensions in the Taiwan Strait Discussion, 2006 March 9 (Box 27, Folder 518)
    Jones Day offices. Presentation by Harry Harding.
  - Ma Ying-Jeou Discussion, 2006 March 20 (Box 27, Folder 519)
  - Jiang Enzhu Luncheon, 2006 March 27 (Box 27, Folder 520)
    Citigroup offices
  - Cheng Li Discussion (The Hu-Bush Summit), 2006 April 17 (Box 27, Folder 521)
  - Hu Jintao Dinner, 2006 April 20 (Box 28, Folder 522)
    Marriott Wardman Park Hotel, Washington, DC. Cosponsored with the US-China Business Council and the US Chamber of Commerce. File includes audience questions.
  - Fortieth Anniversary Program, 2006 May 3 (Box 28, Folder 523)
    New York Athletic Club. The Past as Prologue: A Discussion with the National Committee's Founders, Robert Scalapino and Lucien Pye.
  - Fortieth Anniversary of the NCUSCR - Voice of America Documentary, 2006; DVD (Box 28, Folder 523)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an RAC archivist for further instruction.
    Documentary produced by the Voice of America on four decades of Sino-American relations as seen through the prism of the National Committee.
  - Zhejiang Province Delegation, 2006 May 9 (Box 28, Folder 524)
  - Li Yuanchao Breakfast Program; New York, 2006 May 19 (Box 28, Folder 525)
    Harold Pratt House, Council on Foreign Relations
  - Corporate Philanthropy Roundtable Discussion, 2006 July 11 (Box 28, Folder 526)
    New York Regional Association of Grantmakers
  - China's Judiciary Discussion (Song Jianli), 2006 July 17 (Box 28, Folder 527)
    Jones Day offices
  - Shanghai Cooperation Organization (SCO) E-mail Broadcast, 2006 July 26 (Box 28, Folder 528)
  - Foundation on International and Cross-Straits Studies Roundtable Discussion, 2006 August 23 (Box 28, Folder 529)
  - John Pomfret Program, 2006 September 19 (Box 28, Folder 530)
  - Sino-Japanese Tensions Lecture, 2006 September 21 (Box 28, Folder 531)
    Japan Society
  - John Edwards Interview, 2006 October 31 (Box 28, Folder 532)
  - Annual Members' Program, 2006 November 9 (Box 28, Folder 533)
    Citigroup Center
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences (CASS) Breakfast Discussion, 2006 November 13 (Box 28, Folder 534)
  - Independent Polling Work in China Discussion (Victor Yuan), 2006 December 5 (Box 28, Folder 535)
    Jones Day
  - Fifth Anniversary of China's Accession to the World Trade Organization Reception, 2006 December 14 (Box 28, Folder 536)
    Asian Fusion Galleries
  - Strategic Economic Dialogue; Conference Call, 2006 December 18 (Box 28, Folder 537)
  - Fortieth Anniversary Book (American Participants), 2006 (Box 28, Folder 538)
    "Forty at Forty." On the occasion of its fortieth anniversary, the NCUSCR solicited comments and reflections from twenty American and twenty Chinese participants in its programs. While the files are nominally divided into American and Chinese responses, the responses are intermixed between the files. A set of forty responses is found at the front of this folder, but there is no finished booklet in the file.
  - Fortieth Anniversary Book (Chinese Participants), 2006 (Box 28, Folder 539)
    "Forty at Forty." On the occasion of its fortieth anniversary, the NCUSCR solicited comments and reflections from twenty American and twenty Chinese participants in its programs. While the files are nominally divided into American and Chinese responses, the responses are intermixed between the files.
  - Wang Jisi Program, 2007 March 7 (Box 28, Folder 540)
    Jones Day Offices. Program on Chinese and American Interests in Asia.
  - Bates Gill Program, 2007 April 11 (Box 28, Folder 541)
    Jones Day Offices. Book program, Rising Star: China's New Security Diplomacy.
  - Susan Shirk Program, 2007 April 12 (Box 28, Folder 542)
    World Affairs Council, Washington, DC. Book program, China: Fragile Superpower.
  - Fang Xinghai Program, 2007 April 17 (Box 28, Folder 543)
    UBS offices. Discussion on Developing Shanghai's Financial Sector.
  - Changes and Challenges in Reporting from China Discussion, 2007 April 23 (Box 28, Folder 544)
    Jones Day offices. With Richard Bernstein and Joseph Kahn.
  - Council on Foreign Relations Task Force Report Conference Call Program, 2007 May 1 (Box 28, Folder 545)
  - Annual Members' Program, 2007 May 14 (Box 28, Folder 546)
    New York Athletic Club
  - China Town Hall, 2007 May 31 (Box 28, Folder 547)
    China Town Hall: Local Connections, National Reflections featured a webcast and events in thirty cities throughout the U.S.
  - China Town Hall (Expenses), 2007 May 31 (Box 28, Folder 548)
  - Ambassador Clark T. Randt Jr. Corporate Luncheon, 2007 June 18 (Box 28, Folder 549)
  - Rob Gifford Program (China Road), 2007 July 24 (Box 28, Folder 550)
  - Doing Business with China Program (Ted Plafker), 2007 September 24 (Box 28, Folder 551)
  - China's Participation in International Financial Markets Program, 2007 October 3 (Box 29, Folder 552)
  - Consumer Product Safety Conference Call Program, 2007 October 22 (Box 29, Folder 553)
  - China's Seventeenth Party Congress Program, 2007 October 24 (Box 29, Folder 554)
    Jones Day offices. Speakers, Cheng Li and J. Stapleton Roy.
  - American and Chinese Views Discussion, 2007 December 11 (Box 29, Folder 555)